FAZA MURTADHO

085347223920

faza.murtadho@gmail.com

Sleman, Yogyakarta

<u>LinkedIn</u>

ABOUT



Full Stack Developer with 2 Years of experience creating responsive, user-friendly websites and applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript Framework. Enthusiastic towards new tech in Front End Development for website. Looking to obtain and sharpen skills in the respective area.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Junior Full Stack Web Developer (Full Time)

PT. Softem Mitra Indonesia, Jakarta

December 2022 - March 2024 (1 Year 4 Months)

- Completed 3 months probationary period by developing an internal-use website with React Typescript and Tailwind CSS.
- Assumed responsibility for developing and maintaining internal transaction programs (wholesale products)
 for a Japanese client, utilizing the MVC architecture pattern with C# and ASP.NET during the next three
 months.
- Customizing/rebuilding/reconstructing Japan Prison internal application with React Typescript and Java Spring Boot.
- Continued to manage development, maintenance, bug fixing, and code reviews for Japan Child Consultation internal application using Java Spring Boot framework (Back-End) and Thymeleaf with Bootstrap (Front-End).

Team Leader in Creating Field Monitoring and Administration Mobile Application (Intern)

PT. Kelola Jasa Artha, Surabaya

October 2021 - February 2022 (5 Months)

- Led a cross-functional team in the successful development and launch of a field monitoring and administration mobile application, ensuring adherence to project timelines.
- Creating barcode scanner in mobile application to monitor field staff when distributing money using Android Studio with Java programming language.
- Created UI design for mobile applications using Figma and Android Studio.

Team leader of Business Intelligence Team in the Development of a Web-Based Dashboard Management System for BUMDES NGINGAS during College Community Service (Intern)

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2021 - December 2021 (6 Months)

- Spearheaded a team of 5 members in the development of a user-friendly web-based dashboard management system for BUMDES NGINGAS to help streamline operations and improve decision-making processes.
- Developed a management dashboard using Vue for public access and Power BI for internal reporting, both backed by Laravel and MySQL databases.

Laboratory Assistant at Smart City and Cyber Security

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2019 - July 2021

- Maintained laboratory equipment such as 40 computers, 3 switches, and 1 server.
- Maintained laboratory environment while providing support to lecturers regarding laboratory equipment.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE



Staff at Student Association of Information Technology

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

September 2019 - September 2020

- In charge of guiding new Information Technology students in acclimating to college life and the academic environment.
- Prepared Information Technology students to become members of the Information Technology Student Association.
- Social services

SKILLS



- Front-End Website: Vue, Tailwind CSS, React JS, Thymeleaf, Bootstrap.
- Visual Design: Figma, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe Illustrator.
- Power Bl.

- Other Programming Language: JavaScript, Java Spring Boot, TypeScript, HTML, MVC Architecture.
- Database: Oracle SQL, Microsoft SQL, MySQL.
- Language: English Fluent, Indonesia Native.

EDUCATION



Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science (S. Kom)

GPA: 3.37